[ominous tone plays]
[328] Just go with the umbrella.
and then we're all in.
[454] I'm not going there.
I was line number one.
I was supposed to have first choice.
I'm not moving. His hand was on with you.
[Lorenzo] Yeah! He did! You're dying...
-Go. go!
-Stand your ground. Kevin.
-[man 378] Four. three. two. one.
-Guys. I'm not moving.
[counter beeps]
[woman 328] Oh. wow.
[automated voice] Players.
your two minutes are now over.
You've failed to come
to a unanimous decision
and have broken the rules of the game.
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
[ink packs go off]
[players] No!
[players chatter. laugh. and exclaim]
That's eight people eliminated.
[counter chimes]
Christ. we're gonna lose a lot of people.
[automated voice] Attention. players.
Will the next four players
at the front of each line
please step forward?
[Bryton] All right.
So. hey. come here. come here.
How mad would y'all be
if it came down to somebody
having to pick umbrella.
and I went and got umbrella?
-[man 1] I would be pissed. Don't do it.
-That's fine. Then I won't do it.
-[man 2] I would not be mad.
-You wouldn't be mad?
[man 2] Somebody else
will crack before you.
[automated voice] Attention. players.
The player at the front of each line
should now follow the staff
into the game hall.
That's players 452.
432.
344.
and 299.
to follow the staff into the game hall.
Next up for four is Spencer.
[417] You can't take that umbrella.
-[woman] Take a deep breath. Focus.
-You've got this. You're strong.
He's not the best talker.
Let's go. Spencer!
[ominous music plays]
[woman] Guys. you know.
don't overwhelm him.
[man 1] Yeah. let's give him some space.
[man 107] Listen. bro. Don't move. man.
Take what we are. Our door is "circle."
You stay there.
That is gonna be the best solution.
It should go in order.
It should just be one. two. three. four.
This is based off of luck.
This is based off of what you thought.
He'll... He'll move. You've just got to...
It's who has
the biggest bottle at this point.
You gotta know that I'm not gonna
give y'all umbrella. It's okay.
Stand your ground with four.
[intense musical swell plays]
[sobs]
Hey. Please stop crying. bro.
Jesus Christ.
You're gonna stand there
and endure it. bro.
He'll give you a hard time. but stand
there and endure it. He will give in.
He will give in.
You don't give in.
You've got it. You've got it. dude.
You've got it.
Breathe. Breathe.
[musical swell plays]
[ominous tone plays]
[Spencer] I... I was a mama's boy.
for sure. [laughs]
I remember I used to...
wet the bed a lot.
I used to cry when I was taken
away from my mom.
I don't know. um...
I was very introverted.
and then. as I got older.
it took a long time before I started...
um. getting out of my shell
and talking to people.
Um...
I am extremely gullible. It is a problem.
If someone says something to me.
I'm gonna. like. believe it immediately.
I... I have a... a bunch
of extremely sarcastic siblings.
and I understand it some of the time.
but most of the time.
it goes right over my head.
and I think they're just saying things...
[chuckles] ...truthfully.
Yeah. I think I'm empathetic.
I think to a fault sometimes.
[theme music plays]
[tense rhythmic music plays]
[players applaud and cheer]
[man] You all right?
Let's go. 299.
Be honorable.
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
[clock beeps and ticks]
Listen. listen. Okay.
Are you ready to go home?
-What you wanna say?
-Answer my question.
-Are you ready. yes or no?
-Say what you wanna say.
Are you ready to go home?
It just needs to be one. two. three. four.
If you're ready...
-That's what you want to say?
-Bro. man up. Just man up.
Let's not get shot. bro.
Let's not get shot.
-Yeah. come on. T-man.
-[456] Man up.
-Man up. let's go!
-Man up.
Take the umbrella.
Bro. let's not get shot.
Listen to me real quick. I want you guys
to shut up and listen to me for a second.
[344] Go ahead. bro.
We got a minute and a half left.
I'll pick a frickin' door
if you listen to me!
[Bryton] Just some respect. bro. chill.
-Okay. Relax. we got it.
-You're asking me to respect you.
-And you're not listening to me.
-[344] Come on. bro. Go ahead.
People wanna get out of here
and we got stuff to do.
I'm here to help people.
If I finish my cookie. I'm willing to help
someone else if they allow me.
I'll pick this frickin' umbrella
if you guys promise me...
And I know you all see me.
This sounds so sexual.
Everyone's frigging said it to me.
But spit on someone else's cookie. please.
[344 laughs]
-Lick it.
-I'll spit on your cookie. bro.
I'mma spit right on your cookie.
-What? What?
-[344] Come on. we've got...
I wanna help the other people.
Bro. you don't know
what's behind the door.
If I'm able to do mine.
I will come help you.
-[452] We're all in this.
-Let's go. Let's go.
[ticking]
[tense music plays]
You got 30 seconds to think
and breathe. It's okay. it's okay.
I'll come help you if I finish.
how about that?
Shake my hand. shake my hand.
-Ah. he's breaking. man. He's breaking.
-Oh. God. oh God.
If I finish. I'll come help you. Okay?
Are we trusting the villain right now?
Are we serious?
Is this real life? Is this real life?
-I know you all hear me.
-Come on. bro.
-Please. please. Hand on the wall.
-Ten seconds.
Go to the door. dude. Go to the door!
We're all trying to make it out of here.
[ethereal music plays]
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
[ominous musical flourish plays]
["Gnossienne No.1" by Eric Satie plays]
[beeps]
-[players cheering]
-[man] Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
[sobs]
[vocalizes happily]
[player] We did it!
Oh my God.
We did it. we did it. we did it.
[woman 411] Oh my God.
Sick of this shit. man. He bullied him.
He shook his hand. He's a villain.
You never shake hands with a villain!
[woman] Exactly.
-It's going to be okay.
-Yeah.
[man] It's just an umbrella. We got this.
-You got this.
-Yeah!
It's still... It's still beatable.
bro. you know?
Sweeter victory if we win.
I'm telling you now.
[Spencer sobs]
[automated voice] Attention. players.
Dalgona will begin shortly.
You and your entire line will play
with the shape you have chosen.
Each shape will play independently.
Players will not be permitted
to assist other players.
[Spencer] I was kind of an idiot.
uh. for not expecting this.
I thought...
[inhales sharply]
...that we could help each other. Um...
I don't know.
But... it's a competition.
I should've thought about that sooner.
[man] So. bro. come on.
We got this. We got this. I know.
-[107] I knew there was a twist.
-[woman] A twist.
This is emotional!
[stomach rumbles. swallows]
[Bryton. softly] Oh God. no.
Please don't. please don't. please don't.
-[stomach rumbles]
-Jesus Christ. please don't. Oh God.
[Spencer inhales sharply]
[Spencer grunts weakly]
[chokes softly]
[Bryton. softly] Oh. If he throws up...
[Spencer] I grew up extremely religious
as a member of the Church
of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints.
And I still go to church every week. but...
I'm not sure what I think anymore.
[laughs]
And it's a weird thing to say to people.
but I think questions
are a really important thing in life.
and... it's fine
to not have answers immediately.
I've just had questions for a long time.
and I'm not sure I've been getting
the answers that I wanted.
[keyboard clacking]
-[switch flicks]
-[doors clang and whir]
[automated voice] Players who have
been selected to extract circle
will play first.
Please enter the game hall immediately.
[anxious flute music plays]
[doors clang and whir]
-Yeah!
-[players cheering]
[players] Yes!
-Whoo!
-[man] Yeah!
-So smart. Good job.
-I did. Thank you.
[automated voice] Attention. players.
Please line up
behind the door marked "circle."
The next game is Dalgona.
[suspenseful percussive music plays]
[woman sighs] We got this. Patience.
-[man 1] Let's go. baby.
-[woman] Whoo!
-[man 1] We got this!
-We got this. We all got this.
-Let's go. Come on.
-[Leann chuckles]
Thank you.
[softly] It's a circle.
It's a circle. It's a circle.
[ominous tone plays]
[exhales rapidly]
Oh my God. my hands are shaking.
[automated voice] The time limit
is ten minutes.
With that. let the game begin.
[clock beeps and ticks]
[pulsing ethereal music plays]
[softly] Slow and steady. slow and steady.
[Trey] It's very. very quiet.
[clock ticking]
[needle scraping]
[sighs]
[softly] You can do this.
You can do this. baby. Please.
[Trey] My mom looks focused.
I can't help but think. like.
if I'm gonna win this game.
I need to start playing like my mom.
[automated voice] Player 080. pass.
What did she do to get it out?
-[woman] Spit in the tin.
-Spit in the tin.
[automated voice] Player 278. pass.
[clock continues ticking]
[automated voice] Player 031. pass.
[exclaims happily]
Player 452. pass.
Player 286. pass.
Yes. let's go!
Whoo!
[automated voice] Player 267. pass.
[woman] Good job. baby.
-We got through the hard part. We got it.
-[automated voice] Player 434. pass.
Pass.
[sighs]
[exhales deliberately]
[man] Time?
[woman] Can't look.
-[cracks]
-[woman] Oh. no.
[sighs]
[softly] Love you...
-[ink pack goes off]
-Oh!
[whimpers softly]
[automated voice] Player 048. eliminated.
Player 035. pass.
[snaps]
[ink pack goes off]
Player 428. eliminated.
[cracking]
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 109. eliminated.
Player 188. pass.
What's the time?
-Two thirty-five.
-Come on. I need you to get out.
[automated voice] Player 302. pass.
-[cracks]
-[gasps and sighs]
Cracked. It cracked. y'all.
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 073. eliminated.
[softly] Come on. you're so close. Jess.
You're so close.
You're getting so close. baby. Come on.
You're so close. Come on.
You got it. you got it. Oh my God.
-Please. please. please.
-[automated voice] Player 033. pass.
[sniffles] One-fifteen.
[music intensifying]
[automated voice] Player 301. pass.
[woman] Good job. Trey.
Forty-four seconds. guys.
-Forty seconds.
-[Trey] Forty seconds.
[exhales heavily] You've got it.
you've got it.
you've got it. you've got it.
[automated voice] Player 186. pass.
Yes. Come on. come on. Oh my God.
Twenty seconds left.
-[needle scratching]
-Oh my God. I got it.
[gasps]
-[sighs]
-[automated voice] Player 002. pass.
[continues ticking]
I got it! I got it. I got it.
[sobs]
[breathing heavily]
[clock beeps]
[automated voice] Player 141. pass.
[breath trembling] Oh. I love you.
[keyboard clacks and beeps]
[player laughing]
-[man] Yes!
-[women laugh]
-We're back!
-[woman] We did it! We're back!
We in here!
[all whooping]
[Trey] Yes!
[laughing]
[Leann] Oh my God. I was so worried.
[Trey] Seeing us both in this game
is making me extraordinarily happy.
Every moment I'm spending time
with my mom in here.
I'm like. "I wanna spend
more time with her."
-I made it. I made it. I made it.
-[laughs] I know you made it.
[players chanting] Circle! Circle!
Circle! Circle! Circle! Circle! Circle!
[man] With a special thanks to 452!
-[Dash] 452! Let's go 452!
-[all cheer]
[chanting] 4-5-2! 4-5-2! 4-5-2! 4-5-2!
[doors clang and whir]
[gentle melancholic music plays]
-[man] Oh. Jesus!
-[all exclaim]
-[man 1] Let's go!
-[man 2] Let's go!
[man 3] Man. let's go!
That's what I'm talking about.
-[all yell excitedly]
-[man 4] Let's go. baby! Go.
[Bryton] We've still gotta do it.
We've still gotta do it.
[Bryton] I know I did the right thing.
Somebody had to do it.
Somebody had to put their foot down.
God chose me.
And I mean. I just went with it.
[Bryton] I think
we just have to go for it. Like...
-[man 359] Lick. spit. and just cut?
-Lick. spit. lick. spit.
We do have the easiest one.
but it's still a challenge.
-It's still a challenge. bro.
-Not everybody's gonna pass.
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
-[clock beeps and ticks]
-[Bryton] All right. let's go.
[tense droning music plays]
[Bryton] Does it taste good?
-[man] Yeah. It tastes really good.
-Ah. it does.
[needle scraping]
[Bryton] As an athlete.
I know I'm a competitor.
I'm mentally strong.
Somebody who prepares their mind
for anything to come their way.
But this game is the one
that I'm the most terrified of.
[ticking continues]
It's the one
that you need the most precision.
you need the most patience.
and I'm not really good at that.
My hands are big. My hands are heavy.
Any slight movement and you're done.
[cracking]
[gloomy music plays]
Hope y'all win it. boys.
[ink pack goes off]
[Bryton flaps lips]
[automated voice] Player 456. eliminated.
[Bryton] Oh yes. yes. yes. yes. yes.
[automated voice] Player 382. pass.
-[softly] Oh my God.
-[automated voice] Player 142. pass.
Yes!
Oh my God.
[exhales heavily]
[automated voice] Player 161. pass.
[sighs]
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 020. eliminated.
[automated voice] Player 444. eliminated.
[ink packs go off rapidly]
[automated voice] Player 432. pass.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 165. eliminated.
-Player 222. pass.
-Good luck. good luck.
Sorry. brother.
[Bryton] I'm not thinking
about the other people here.
At the end of the day.
only the strong survive.
and I'm here for myself.
I'm the only person
that truly has my back.
-[cheering and applauding]
-[man] Hey!
[man 286] My boy! What's up?
[man] Oh my God.
-[Trey] Nice work. man.
-Let's go. let's go.
[woman] 432. good game. man.
I saw you. Good negotiating.
-You're welcome. you're welcome.
-Thank you.
-[286] Great speech too. Great speech.
-[Bryton] Great speech?
I think that he's gonna
get eliminated soon.
-432?
-Yeah.
Thank you for picking for us. dude.
[434] Bro. I was a circle.
but that was a big dick move.
I like how you played that.
[woman] People do not like him in here.
I almost wanna. like. seep
into the background here more.
for the long game 'cause I'm not trying
to be the loudest person here.
432's the loudest person here.
You ain't gonna be louder than him.
-Congratulations. man.
-You too. you too.
Live to fight another day.
[woman 179] 432 has been very loud.
outspoken. arrogant.
Just rubbing people. like. the wrong way.
We're all here for a reason.
We're here to win a prize.
But that can also be won with humility.
Okay. so there's actually less people
in here than I thought.
A lot less. This is circle and triangle.
-Circle and triangle. yeah.
-Now they have star.
I think it goes down to 90.
[doors clang and whir]
[tense music playing]
[Dani] I'mma see all of y'all
in the dorm tonight.
[softly] Good luck.
You got this. You're good.
[Dani] I do have insecurities.
I... I am scared about people trusting me.
I'm scared about
the way people perceive me.
Like. if they like me.
if they think I'm funny.
or they think I'm charming.
things like that.
I'm insecure about how
I don't have. like. a boyfriend.
a serious relationship at the age of 23.
All my friends are getting married
or are pregnant and having kids.
I'm insecure. like.
why does no one like me?
Part of this experience
is proving to myself
that I'm capable of doing something crazy.
But... to. like. like yourself
and love yourself
and. like. the flaws. and...
I think that... that's really difficult.
to process that I don't
really like or love myself
at the point that I'm at right now.
[sparse intriguing music plays]
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 219. eliminated.
[clock continues ticking]
[man] Come on.
-[snaps]
-[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 079. eliminated.
[music intensifies]
[Dani] I am terrified to breathe.
Scared that any noise
would break the cookie.
-[cracks]
-[gasps softly]
[sighs]
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 039. eliminated.
[inhales sharply]
[Dani] I'm thinking
about player 200 still.
And how I did him dirty.
[automated voice] Player 451. pass.
[woman] Good job. Phill.
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
[groans]
I chose to hurt somebody
instead of help someone.
and karma's a bitch.
I had it coming.
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 134. eliminated.
[suspenseful percussive music plays]
[ticking continues]
[man groans]
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 245. eliminated.
Player 287 and player 198. pass.
[man 198] Yes.
[automated voice] Player 337. pass.
Player 344. pass.
[music intensifies]
Yes.
[automated voice] Player 243. pass.
Player 016. pass.
Player 176. pass.
Yes. God!
[beeps]
[automated voice] The game is now over.
[keyboard clacks]
-[button beeps]
-[ink packs go off repeatedly]
[automated voice] Player 092. 262.
265. 285. 322. 345.
eliminated.
[swallows]
Players who have been selected
to extract umbrella.
please now enter the game hall.
-Let's go.
-Let's go. let's go.
[Kyle] The atmosphere in our line
is definitely anger with 299.
I cannot believe
that he settled with umbrella.
I do not like player 432.
but I would've rather been in their line.
as our chances
of moving further in this game
was just cut very. very slim.
[doors whir]
[man] Bro...
-Can't even look us in the eyes.
-[man 003] Mm-hmm.
[Spencer] I hear their whispers.
calling me things.
[man 1] Idiot.
[Spencer] And I see their glances.
-[man 2] Is he in here?
-[flaps lips]
[woman whispers] He's... He's over there.
I'm here 'cause I wanna be able
to help my parents out financially and...
[sniffles] I put that on the line.
but I put that on the line
for everyone else.
I think there's
a huge target on my back now.
[woman 361] I say more of us go back
than the rest of them. so...
[chuckles]
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
[beeps and ticks]
Okay. [sighs]
[droning music plays]
[needles scraping]
-[man] Put the saliva on the top.
-The top works really well for me.
[man] Yeah. yeah.
[mutters indistinctly]
-[stomach rumbling]
-[swallows]
[retches]
[continues ticking]
[Kyle] I am trying
to cancel everything out.
I don't want any distraction at all
'cause I'm already worried.
[needles scraping]
[man exhales heavily]
[Kyle] The stakes are. like.
through the roof for me right now.
[breathing heavily]
I... I mean. it's... it's almost unbearable.
The amount of money
that this needle is in control of...
[cracks]
[Kyle groans]
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 101. eliminated.
-[cracking]
-Shit.
[gasps softly]
It was a good game. guys. Good luck.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 193. eliminated.
[breath catching]
[swallows]
[Spencer] I'm feeling pressure
on my shoulders.
I can't look around. or I might puke.
I was this close.
-[ink pack goes off]
-Oh!
[automated voice] Player 349. eliminated.
[stomach rumbles]
[Spencer] But it's really hard to not see
all the other people around me.
[ink pack goes off]
-[Spencer] And what they're losing...
-[automated voice] Player 335. eliminated.
...because of what I did.
-[cracks]
-Oh. so close.
Damn it.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[swallows]
[automated voice] Player 006. eliminated.
-Player 067. eliminated.
-[ink pack goes off]
Player 338. eliminated.
[Spencer] I think
some of them are gonna hate me.
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 137. eliminated.
I think some of them are going to. like.
remember me for the rest of their life
as the person who ruined their chance
of becoming a millionaire.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 274. eliminated.
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 114. eliminated.
[Spencer] It's almost finished.
and I'm extremely excited and nervous.
This is gonna be a win for me.
[belches. stomach rumbles]
-[cracks]
-[gasps and squeals]
-[breathing heavily]
-[stomach continues rumbling]
[swallows forcefully]
[Spencer] They say they're games. [laughs]
But they're not.
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 299. eliminated.
Yes. Oh!
[automated voice] Player 270. pass.
-Oh. man.
-[automated voice] Player 215. pass.
I knew it. I could tell. He's good.
[bold music playing]
[sighs]
Need to speed up a bit. I think.
[ink pack goes off]
[automated voice] Player 004. eliminated.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 368. eliminated.
-[automated voice] Player 223. eliminated.
This is a struggle. bro.
Oh my God. I nearly got it out.
I'm so angry.
Together.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[both gasp]
[continues ticking]
Come on. Yes. Come on. Little more.
[automated voice] Player 330. pass.
Player 367. pass.
Player 194. pass.
-How many seconds?
-[man] Thirty.
No.
-[ink pack goes off]
-[automated voice] Player 021. eliminated.
God. this is so gentle.
I just need to get it out.
-Uh...
-[automated voice] Player 107. pass.
-Done. Let's go.
-[automated voice] Player 418. pass.
How many seconds? How many seconds?!
[man] Five seconds.
It's stuck. it's stuck. it's stuck.
I got it. I got it!
[clock beeps]
[automated voice] Player 319. pass.
Let's go!
-We both made it! Oh my God.
-We made it!
[automated voice] Your time is now up.
["I Want A Little Sugar In My Bowl"
by Nina Simone plays]
♪ I want a little sugar ♪
♪ In my bowl ♪
[whispers] So close. So close.
♪ I want a little sweetness
Down in my soul ♪
♪ I could stand some loving ♪
♪ Oh so bad ♪
♪ I feel so funny ♪
♪ I feel so sad ♪
[ink pack goes off]
♪ I want a little steam ♪
♪ On my clothes ♪
♪ What's the matter. Daddy? ♪
♪ Come on. save my soul ♪
♪ I need some sugar in my bowl ♪
♪ I ain't fooling ♪
♪ I want some sugar. mmm ♪
♪ In my bowl ♪
-Honey. we're home!
-Hey.
[players cheering]
-Yes!
-[man 030] Oh my God.
Oh my God.
I'm so happy to see all your faces.
[man 107] Umbrella gang in the house!
Mary Poppins is the best.
[cheering and laughing]
[Stephen] Dude. my heart
just started racing.
Dude. I thought that big hair was Kyle.
He's 101.
Where is he?
[Bryton] It was crazy. bro.
[man 107] I thought I was gone.
I thought I was done. bro.
[sinister music plays]
The three people I wanted out.
all three of them
came back from their shapes.
-It was...
-Who did you want out?
Uh. Adrian.
I thought I was never gonna see
your faces again.
-I know.
-I was getting so upset.
Theo and Bryton.
Give me a hug.
Dude.
-[man 107] I can't lie.
-Good job. my boy.
I think some of these power players
need to be taken out.
107. not only finishing the umbrella.
like. oh my God. what a warrior.
he also finished first
in Red Light. Green Light.
You gotta eliminate the guy
that's winning all the challenges.
But top of the list. 432.
If I ever get a chance
to eliminate a player.
I will eliminate 432.
-[Bryton] Bruh.
-NFL. F**** NFL.
[Bryton] I'm not in the NFL!
-[man 198] You little frat boy.
-Come here.
Let me tell you something.
Nah. don't run away.
Nah. don't run now.
your little skinny ass.
-[man 198] You gonna...
-I will snap your ass over my knee.
-Do it.
-If I come down there. will you run?
-[man 198] No. no.
-Okay.
-Come on. let's go.
-Where are we going?
-Don't run now.
-No. where are we going?
Look. let me tell you something.
Come here. I'm not touching you.
Don't touch me. I'm not touching you.
If you call me a frat boy again...
I won't put my hands on you
'cause I won't.
[man 198] Right.
But when we get off this bitch.
I might. Okay?
-All right. frat boy.
-Cool.
-Hey. uh... [scoffs]
-All right.
432 is like. um. one of them lads
who thinks he's still in high school
and. like. thinks it's cool
to talk shit to everyone.
Um. I don't think anyone
is actually scared of him.
They just all don't like him.
I don't think he realizes that.
God. I hate him.
But if I get the chance.
I'll just eliminate him.
[woman 1] Here. I'll pass
the washing liquid over here.
[woman 2] Oh my God.
There's hair all over this floor.
-That's gnarly.
-I know.
Ugh. I thought
they were cleaner than this. Honestly.
I think they're gonna make
an announcement.
-Oh. Oh. damn. It's so dry.
-[woman] See what I'm saying?
They trying to kill me.
trying to take me out the game.
It's so dry. bro.
[automated voice] Attention. players.
Told you.
[tense music plays]
Here are the results of the second game.
[players exclaim and applaud]
[man 1] Yes.
-[woman] Whoo!
-[man 2] Yeah.
Oh. snap.
Get out here. get out here!
[Stephen] We gotta get up for this.
[man 136] Now this I wanna see.
Here we go. here we go. here we go.
["The Marriage of Figaro" by Mozart plays]
Oh!
-Keep going.
-Keep moving. keep moving.
[man] Oh my God!
[man 396] Oh! Nailed it!
Wow.
$3.3 million.
Oh. man.
[automated voice] Out of 188 players.
69 have been eliminated.
That's a lot.
[cheering and applauding]
-I'm not clapping for that.
-Yeah. those are our friends.
[Leann] Yeah. I'm not clapping.
[button beeps]
[ominous music plays]
Yes.
Oh. it's big piggy.
[bank chiming digitally]
-[Stephen] Yeah. buddy.
-[man 336] Whoo!
[automated voice] The prize money
accumulated so far is $3.37 million.
Oh my God. [chuckles]
We deserve this.
That's it.
[man 336] And somebody here
is gonna win that. Isn't that nuts?
It's pretty cool. man.
[Stephen] I wanna get that money.
but I know I need to go make some friends
because. after Dalgona.
I've lost half of my alliance.
My boy 101 Kyle was in the fourth line.
my fellow mullet boy.
and he never showed back up.
I don't know about you guys.
I feel a little bit sad. All my guys gone.
My best friend Chase was here with me
in Red Light. Green Light.
They zapped him
almost first things first. eliminated.
I think it's very important
to have an alliance
just in case
we're able to pick our own teams.
especially if it comes to the tug-of-war.
But it looks like this
is the new crew right here.
Yeah. Right here.
[Stephen] It's the new little alliance.
Got some brains. little bit of strength.
-Little old man strength.
-[Stephen] We got the wisdom.
We need to come up with a team name.
Gganbu.
-Gganbu. yeah. Gganbu gang.
-Gganbu?
-That means "best friends" in Korea.
-Best friends. yeah. Gganbu.
Gganbu gang?
-Yeah. gganbu gang.
-[Stephen] I like it.
[Rick] I like to have strategy
and... and... and a game plan.
Um. you know. I found the allies.
the gganbu gang.
that can help me win this.
And. uh. I think we're a very strong gang.
And. uh... And if... if we lose.
whatever the game is.
I'm losing with friends.
and I can handle that very easily.
Hey. knucks it in the middle.
[all] Gganbu gang.
-Gganbu gang. whoo!
-I like it. That's pretty freakin' cool.
What shapes did you have?
I had the easy. Circle.
-I feel bad. [laughs]
-Don't. Was you in... I had the circle!
I had an umbrella. [laughs]
You need that. like. tattooed
on you or something.
-I'm gonna tattoo a circle. are you?
-Yeah.
[Leann] I am in this game
more as a personal challenge.
[gentle music plays]
I wanna do it to prove I still have...
the thing that's inside me
that I haven't seen for a long time.
I want the opportunity...
to show you can keep trying new things
and doing new things.
And I wanted to prove it to myself.
So... thought this is
a good chance to do that. I think.
I don't know what to expect.
but... I think this is a good chance
to... meet people from all over the world.
And I hope I make friends that I'll have.
So I'm excited about it.
I'm really not scared.
I'm... I'm just excited about it.
I don't think the men
generally realize what women have.
-It's discounted. you know?
-[367] But maybe that's for the best.
I love just being able
to have people think I'm the underdog.
But. that aside.
do you think it's key
to get to know. shall we say...
-For the purpose of teamwork?
-...some of the big. strong ones?
These are the strategies
that we need to be drawing on
when we look at tug-of-war
'cause that's next.
[Leann] Right.
[beeps]
[ominous music plays]
-[man 1] Oh. wait.
-[man 2] Oh. Oh!
[man 1] Yo.
[man 3] Something going on.
There's something going on.
-Here we go.
-[man 4] Who's picking up the phone?
Don't touch it. Don't touch it.
Don't touch it. Don't touch it!
Don't touch it! [laughs]
It's got to be something like a test.
I'm just hanging. kind of just watching.
'Cause I don't wanna be involved
in anything.
I don't want people to know who I am.
If this pho...
this whole phone thing is a test.
why would they choose me for elimination.
when they don't know I exist?
-[man 1] Maybe we can call someone?
-Pick it up. Somebody pick it up.
-[man 2] I'll pick it up.
-L-Let it ring first. Let it ring.
-Oh. Oh!
-[players exclaim]
Leave it.
This shit ain't gonna be...
It's not gonna be f...
[woman 1] Shh!
[woman 278] Just pick it up.
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
There's nothing. There's nothing.
They look like a bunch of monkeys
that don't know what the hell it is.
God damn it.
I just think I need to get
to that phone first. before anyone else.
Who do you reckon... Okay.
If you had the option to eliminate.
who's your number one?
-432. I think.
-Yeah. that'd be it.
-Are you okay?
-[Bryton] No.
-You didn't eat. did you?
-Mm-mmm.
-I'm just trying to conserve my energy.
-I know.
432 is out there. He's brash.
And I'm not here to be everyone's mom.
but I just wanted to talk to him
to see if he reall...
if that really was who he was.
The people that don't like me in here
have no sense of humor.
-Or they interpret you differently.
-Differently. yeah.
They interpret you as abrasive. and like...
-You know?
-Yeah. and it... that's just not it at all.
-Like... Yeah.
-Well. you talk. you don't think.
It's just purely intrinsic. like...
-Yeah. it's because...
-"I'm out there immediately."
And it can be interpreted
as abrasive. you know?
But you have to realize if people think
that I'm not gonna be myself
for a split second...
-Is it totally yourself?
-One thousand percent.
See? That's... Then that's what you are.
He isn't. like. putting on a face.
He... It's who he is.
My only thought. um. with 432 is. like.
if we are ever going to play tug-of-war.
he has the strength
to make up having me on his team.
-Someone said you played in college?
-Yes. ma'am.
-What'd you play?
-Football.
-Where?
-Clemson.
The Tigers.
-Yeah.
-And did... did you graduate?
No. ma'am. I drop...
I dropped out to come here.
I have one semester left.
So. why'd you come? Why'd you come here?
I like challenges.
so I can talk about it later in life.
Like. I was raised.
and I had to learn everything on my own.
Like. yeah. my mom worried.
and she stressed.
Your dad wasn't around?
No. it was just me and my mom.
-Aw.
-Just... She was my best friend. but...
-It is what it is.
-Well. you're a good son.
-I try.
-You're not abrasive.
I know I'm not.
-But 120 people think I am.
-[laughs]
-Well. 119.
-No. there's fewer than that.
[Bryton] From the moment
that I was put on this Earth.
it was just me and my mom.
So there was no trust from. like. uh.
a father standpoint.
or there was no trust from.
um.
I don't know.
I wasn't really born into trust.
I wasn't...
The only person I could trust was my mom.
And at times.
I couldn't even trust my mom because...
How much can...
My mom had me when she was 21.
so how much can a 20-year-old white woman
teach a young Black kid?
Like. there's only so much
that she could do.
so I trusted her with everything.
You know. don't get it wrong.
I... I love her to death.
That... That is. like. my best friend
on this planet.
But you gotta understand
that from the moment
I was put on this Earth.
there was...
There wasn't really anybody
for me to trust.
for me to just. like...
Nobody understood who I was.
and I still
don't think anybody really does.
[musical swell plays and intensifies]
[Husnain] Imagine if it just rang now.
[man] We're gonna do a three-part breath
that basically goes like this.
So you're gonna open your mouth
wider than is comfortable.
You're gonna breathe into the belly first.
A breath like... [gasps]
[inhales sharply]
Then blow it out. [breathes forcefully]
So it's gonna be work. all right?
[man 330] The last couple of days
have been crazy.
Little sleep. bunch of stress.
and so many people are up in their heads.
As a performance and longevity doctor.
I know that when we are
in our stress state.
it takes us out of who we really are.
So I really learned
to actually calm people down.
and put them in the thrive state.
who they authentically are.
I'm all for bringing people
back to the present.
Be in this moment
right now.
A cheerleader.
whenever they jump in the air.
they spread their legs in air.
and they touch their toes.
[Dr. V] All right. let's...
-You got it. bro.
-Beautiful.
[Dr. V] Predictions for... for the day?
I predict they're gonna call
and ask for a number to answer the phone.
and that number will be eliminated.
[Bryton] So it's like... [grunts]
[tense music plays and intensifies]
-[rings]
-[Bryton] Oh. the phone's ringing.
[woman] Phone's ringing.
He can answer it all he wants.
[continues ringing]
I wanna answer this phone
in hope that I get to eliminate someone.
I wanna eliminate 432.
What's the worst that can happen?
Hello?
[player shushing]
[Bryton] I feel like he answered it
a little too fast.
[Husnain] Hello?
Hey. hey. he's been standing
by the phone this whole time.
-[automated voice] Player.
-Yeah.
Do not hang up this call
until you are told to do so.
[Bryton] He's been standing by the phone
this whole time. waiting for it to ring.
[automated voice] As a result
of answering this call...
Because I've answered this call...
[players shushing]
Please let me eliminate someone.
He's getting cocky.
I wanna eliminate him right now. 432.
...you will be given
the opportunity to enjoy a treat.
[buzzer plays on speaker]
Here we go.
[woman] Oh. boy.
[door whirring]
-[players exclaim]
-Oh! What?
-[man 1] Oh. dude. is that a cheeseburger?
-No way.
Is that actual food?
Oh. damn!
-[players exclaiming]
-[woman 1] Oh! Oh my God!
It's a burger and fries.
[man 2] Yo. yo. yo. yo. yo!
Move back y'all. move back!
Oh my God. it smells so good.
[man 3] No!
-[man 002] Oh my God. what? You're joking.
-[man 4] Take it! Take it!
-[players yell]
-[man 5] No way. No way! No!
[man 6] It's every man for himself. bro.
[woman 2] Can I have a fry?
Scavengers. man.
[man 7] Whoa. whoa!
-Oh my God.
-No way. That girl got a full burger.
-[woman 3] She ran away with it.
-[woman 4] Come on.
I took that big. fat. juicy burger.
and I was feeling great.
Top ten meal I've ever had in my life.
That's the best burger ever.
[ominous music plays]
[man 176] Wow. guys. Wow.
Okay. how about we split this?
Wait. wait. wait. this was my treat.
[man 10] Can I have
these two French fries?
Scavengers.
When I was looking at that food.
I was. like. disappointed.
Like. I know it was food.
and it was. like. nice.
But I wanted to eliminate 432.
Ew! Bro. y'all are actually
low-key kind of disgusting.
Like. this is actually disgusting.
Like. how stupid can y'all actually be?
I wasn't even arsed about the food.
I wanted to eliminate someone.
Who? I guess whoever took the burger.
No. 432. He said
that he was gonna snap me in half.
-[woman 355] That was you?
-Yeah.
-I don't wanna touch that phone.
-I'm not answering a random phone.
What if I answer the phone.
and they're like. "Okay."
"We have a deep-dish pizza
back here just for you
if you eliminate one person"?
-Yep. pizza.
-I wouldn't blame you.
I don't think I could do it
because I'm not an asshole.
[man] What you do is you go back there.
eat the pizza.
but don't tell anybody you got pizza.
That would be the most selfish move.
[tense ethereal music plays]
[Husnain] Something's gonna happen.
and I'm gonna answer.
[Lorenzo] I'm... Maybe I'm gonna pick up
the phone next.
-[254] No. don't do that.
-I feel like it's gonna be bad next time.
They're baiting you
to pick up the phone now.
Mmm.
You want... You want a Happy Meal
or do you want four million quid?
Oh my God. Right now?
[chuckles] I'm not sure.
[women laugh]
-Them chicken nuggets? Oh my God!
-[man 254] Oh. leave him alone!
[Husnain] Ring the phone... now.
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
[phone rings]
[man 1] Oh. there it goes.
-[woman] The phone's ringing.
-[man 2] Who's getting it?
[Husnain] Shall I answer?
Shall I answer it?
I'm gonna answer it. I'm gonna answer it.
Do you wanna answer it?
-[phone continues ringing]
-[players] No!
Please. not him. Not him again.
Oh my God.
Hello?
[automated voice] Player. do not hang up
this call until you are told to do so.
I'm just genuinely surprised
that he's picked it up twice.
If he gets another hamburger.
I'm gonna be mad.
[automated voice] Player 198.
Yes. sir.
[automated voice] As a result
of answering this call.
you... are now at risk of being eliminated.
[dramatic musical flourish plays]
Shit.
[suspenseful music plays]
[automated voice] You must convince
another player to pick up this call.
[355] Curiosity. [chuckles]
[automated voice] When another player
accepts the phone.
they will be at risk of elimination.
Ah.
-What's going on?
-I. like. wanna walk away now.
We're. like. "Bye."
They all walked away.
[automated voice] The time limit
is two minutes.
If you fail to convince
another player to take the phone.
you will be eliminated.
He's definitely looking over here.
At us?
[bold music playing]
I think I'm gonna try to go up here.
[automated voice] Player 198.
do you understand?
Yes.
Your time starts now.
[bold music intensifying]
[dramatic musical flourish plays]
[ominous closing theme music plays]